I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
So, how was it?
Pretty scary, that Leon Sykes.
Will we be able to go on at Grateful Sound?
He said he'd have to look into it.
Look into it, huh?
Just make sure you pay back the money
for your expenses within this month, okay?
He's the kind of guy who'd
kill Erica Blige for money.
Yeah...I'll be careful.
Don't want to lose my life over that.
Anyways...Pay it back quickly, okay?
Hmph. Don't worry. I'm not
getting bumped off just yet.
Just pay it back, 'kay?
Hiromi-chan, you bought all these?
Yeah, they're from a used-book store,
but now I can learn lots of songs,
and play my heart out.
You're really into it.
I'll look bad if I owned a guitar
and couldn't play a tune.
Yeah.
But these books are so hard to read...
I wouldn't depend on these books entirely.
There are lots of mistakes here.
Huh? Then how am I supposed to learn?
Well, it's best to listen to
the songs and then copy them.
But I think it's up to the individual.
For me, I'd get a book
on how to play chords,
and practice that like heck.
Would those books show the
finger placement of the chords?
Yup, you press the strings and strum.
I just practiced learning those chords.
Then were you able to
learn the songs by ear?
Ahh...Well, I did ask others too.
That's incredible!
You are a genius, Koyuki-kun!
Oh-oh yeah? I think I'm pretty ordinary.
I'd still say you've got a good ear though.
Anyway, practice makes perfect, I guess.
I don't care how gifted you may be,
you don't just wake up
one day knowing all this.
You really think so?
I...really don't have
much else I'm good at,
and I love playing the guitar...
And I've never once
gotten tired of playing.
Well, maybe just once...
Uh! Yeah!
You open up the door
with negative aura
You say future is murky indeed...
-Without Lucille,
-You say future is murky indeed...
-I'm sick of hearing gripe.
-Ryusuke now plays on a custom Les Paul.
-Open up the door with negative aura
-But still, it's not Lucille,
-If you never change
-and Ryusuke isn't entirely satisfied.
-I think there is no way my life
-From our jam sessions
based on Ryusuke's riffs,
-fizzle out
we've come up with
this song, "Brainstorm."
-This is our most powerful
-You open up the door
with negative aura
-and best song yet.
-(I'm fed up fed up fed up)
-And best song yet.
-You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Open up the door with negative aura
(I can't keep up with you)
I think there is no way my life
-Fizzle out
-Should we release a new CD by this Fall?
-What!?
Hey, Ryusuke!
We don't have any feature songs.
You want to do a collection of covers?
Nah, we're going to make new songs.
Huh?
We made a CD that hit the
top ten college charts in the US,
it'd be sad if we didn't
release a follow-up.
Well, that's your fault!
Anyway...
Let's make another CD.
Then what are we going to do
about the Grateful Sound thing?
I haven't heard back from Leon yet.
Geez, I guess we can't
count on Leon, either.
Well, there's nothing we can do about that.
Yeah, I know, but still...
-Please come see us! We're Beck!
-Please come see us!
We're Beck. Please come see us!
They're called "Beck."
That's weird. Couldn't they
come up with a different name?
I've always wondered...
Is it worth passing out these flyers?
It's true that these expenses do add up.
It's important to get the word out.
If even one person came to
see us because of this flyer,
that one person could help
spread the word about us.
Hi there! Our band's call Beck!
Please come see us play!
What the heck's this?
Wow, it's incredible...
So, this is our competition today?
They're called "Beck."
What a joke of a name.
Hey, I read in a magazine...
That kid with the cap there, he had
a bit part in that Dying Breed movie.
Oh?
Yeah, heard they got quite
a reception at the Whiskey a GoGo.
They're probably just a poser band,
flavor of the month.
It'll be tough for them to
survive here at the Marquee.
It's survival of the fittest here...
These guys will probably just fade away.
Uh! Yeah!
You open up the door
with negative aura
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
-We might be the ones...
-I'm sick of hearing gripe.
-Open up the door with negative aura
-Getting shut out.
-So, what do you think of Beck, Manager?
-If you never change
-I think there is no way my life
-fizzle out
Looks like they won't be quitting
the live house for a while.
You open up the door
with negative aura
(I'm fed up fed up fed up)
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Hey, did you see that Shibuya one?
Yeah, Yoshito's so cool!
I'm totally into him!
"Yoshito-Shibuya Panic"
That must have been
an excellent promotion.
Seems like the Grateful Sound
tickets are selling well too.
Shibuya Panic, huh?
Sounds like a take on a promotion that
the Stones did long ago in New York.
The Stones, huh?
They're in a whole 'nother league from us.
Hey, to each his own.
We'll just do things our way.
Huh? Ryusuke-kun!
Hmm? Oh, Koyuki.
"Shiina Bookstore"
We were on our way to the Fishing Hole.
I have something I wanted to give to Maho.
"Shiina Bookstore"
She's there now.
"Fishing Hole"
Hey there, Koyuki!
Um, this...It's from my parents.
What is it?
It's Kishu Ume.
(Pickled plums, Kishu-style)
You were gobbling them up the last time.
Thanks.
Oh, let me introduce you,
she's my classmate, Melanie.
F-fine, thank you. How are you?
No one's asking how you're doing!
You're funny.
J-Japanese?
Yeah, despite the way she looks,
Melanie was born in Japan.
She's fluent in Japanese. Don't sweat it.
Maho stayed overnight at your place, right?
Wasn't her teeth-grinding something else?
Ah, well...no...
Her teeth-grinding is unbelievable!
Even Yoshito said so.
Oh, shut up!
Why are you talking about that?
I see...
Huh?
For Maho, it's nothing unusual
to sleep over at a friend's house...
I guess I was the only one
getting all nervous over it.
Americans are so progressive...
Huh? Chiba's going to be there?
Yup, he said he'll be on about 10 o'clock.
He said if we mention his name at
the door, they'll let us in for free.
That Chiba...What's he planning?
Ah!
Wake up at 11 in the morning,
the ideal break
Turn off the switch from this rapid speed,
take a quick smoke, instantly hungry
Eat move eat embrace relax embrace
sleep and relax again happiness
Let the tension go mellow today
straight to the brain, simply flow
Turning my ear, the rhythm of
the sound and words-die hard
Right, how is it? This feeling!
He was really in his element, huh.
I wonder if Chiba plans to leave Beck,
and go with this band.
No, this is his way of training.
It really bothers him that he's the
only one who didn't see that dream.
Chiba's the kind of guy who'd go tattoo
"Mongolian Chop Squad" on his back.
What a fool...That Chiba.
We wouldn't fire our band's front man
just because of some dream.
Yeah.
Huh?
Maho?
Yo!
A-ho! A-ho!
Ah, oh...
That's strange, his wings are clipped,
so he shouldn't be able
to fly away very far...
When's Mr. Saito coming
back from his business trip?
Tomorrow...
Koyuki, you're really fond
of Mr. Saito, aren't you?
You think so? Well, he is
my guitar instructor after all.
Your mom was telling me
over breakfast last time...
Huh? What did she say?
That when you were little
you were a bit odd,
and she was worried about your future.
Hmm. Yeah, she says that once in a while.
But I don't remember anything
from when I was little.
So none of the things
she said I did seem real.
Seems you were strange enough,
climbing on top of the table
and singing and stuff...
Yeah, but now, I'm just
an ordinary, teenage guy.
Well, I better get going.
Huh?
Make sure you thank your mom
for me for the pickled plums.
Oh, you're not coming over?
I'll catch the last train out
tonight to get home.
'Cause, when I'm alone with you,
I get kinda nervous
and can't sleep too well.
Uh...I'll walk you to the station.
Uh-huh.
Koyuki, I don't think
you're just an ordinary guy.
You think so?
I hope you find Page.
Well, see yah!
Thanks. Take care.
In order to survive, without realizing it,
I've adapted myself
to society's expectations.
"If you live life by
other people's standards,
then your life is no longer yours."
That's what Eddy said.
If I really thought about what
it means to live life and to die,
I may be the one who needs
to reassess things.
What?! Page was singing along with you?
Then it must be a great song!
Yeah, but I've only gotten
part of the refrain done.
Hmm...
If he didn't interrupt, I think I would
have had the whole song finished.
But after struggling to
catch Page, it all went away.
It just came to you?
It seems so strange
when I think of it now.
When I was trying to compose
a song, I couldn't at all.
Then all of a sudden,
this melody just popped up in my head.
Well, let's hear it!
Okay.
Koyuki, you really wrote that tune?
Uh-huh.
Then, where should I go?
Okay, I know that. What time?
Okay. I'll be there.
Hey, It's my first time
to ride on a helicopter.
I brought this again, for Beck. Take it.
"Dog Arnold's Bone" [Doggie Treats]
Hey, you fuckin' talk too much.
Shoot me if you want, all right?
You think I won't shoot you
right here, muthafucker?
Hey, stop it! We're talking business here.
So, where are you going?
North.
Damn, fucker! Always getting me
in trouble with the boss.
Yukio! It's your favorite, stew!
Damn, this fucker's
always doing this shit...
Hello. Good morning.
Do you know who this is?
There's only one woman that I know
with a whiskey-soaked,
raspy voice like yours.
It's been decided.
You guys will be going on
the Grateful Sound stage.
Yeah.
There was a real push from Leon.
Even Ran couldn't resist.
Hey Aunty, it's not finalized yet.
Huh? What do you mean?
I still have to run it
by the rest of the band.
But don't you guys want to
perform at Grateful Sound?
Yesterday, I met with Leon.
We even went to look at the stage.
So...what happened?
His terms were way too hard.
I don't think we can go through with it.
Hello, Ryusuke-kun?
What's up? Koyuki, come help me
set up the fishing poles.
Umm, I wanted you to listen to this.
Hmm. I'm surprised
you wrote such a tune.
Really?
But the continuity is off.
I see.
All right! I've decided, Koyuki.
Hmm? Decided what?
We're going to appear at Grateful Sound!
H-Hey! I-I-Is this for real?!
U-Us! Hah-hah!
-Yeah!
-Dying Breed's not appearing?
No, I don't want to trouble Eddy.
I see. So what were Leon's terms?
We'll talk about it later.
Right now, I just want to focus
on improving the band's skills.
Chiba-kun! I'm sure
they'll give you one if you ask.
Yeah, is that so?
You sure like to pilfer stuff.
Shut up, you!
An incredible summer...
A really incredible summer
is about to unfold...
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day
What a fool
I don't know 'bout tomorrow
What it's like to be
Ah...
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Full moon sways
Smiling in my arms for all those years
We're finally headed North.
Destination: Grateful Sound!
"Live 22 'Performance Eve Festival"'
Next episode, Performance Eve Festival!
Watch it, okay?